[
  { "question": "ناروتو", "answer": "ن ا ر و ت و" },
  { "question": "انجيلو عمك", "answer": "ا ن ج ي ل و ع م ك" },
  { "question": "ارليكينو", "answer": "ا ر ل ي ك ي ن و" },
  { "question": "الهيثم", "answer": "ا ل ه ي ث م" },
  { "question": "هيرو", "answer": "ه ي ر و" },
  { "question": "هوليا", "answer": "ه و ل ي ا" },
  { "question": "هيرا", "answer": "ه ي ر ا" },
  { "question": "هيستوريا", "answer": "ه ي س ت و ر ي ا" },
  { "question": "هومورا", "answer": "ه و م و ر ا" },
  { "question": "هيماواري", "answer": "ه ي م ا و ا ر ي" },
  { "question": "جاكس", "answer": "ج ا ك س" },
  { "question": "جيمي", "answer": "ج ي م ي" },
  { "question": "سيبر", "answer": "س ي ب ر" },
  { "question": "جان", "answer": "ج ا ن" },
  { "question": "جيرايا", "answer": "ج ي ر ا ي ا" },
  { "question": "يوميكو", "answer": "ي و م ي ك و" },
  { "question": "شوكو", "answer": "ش و ك و" },
  { "question": "ايري", "answer": "ا ي ر ي" },
  { "question": "لولوش", "answer": "ل و ل و ش" },
  { "question": "اثي", "answer": "ا ث ي" },
  { "question": "يوتا", "answer": "ي و ت ا" },
  { "question": "فيودور", "answer": "ف ي و د و ر" },
  { "question": "دازاي", "answer": "د ا ز ا ي" },
  { "question": "اوتا", "answer": "ا و ت ا" },
  { "question": "سانجي", "answer": "س ا ن ج ي" },
  { "question": "ريكا", "answer": "ر ي ك ا" },
  { "question": "باغي", "answer": "ب ا غ ي" },
  { "question": "ميراجين", "answer": "م ي ر ا ج ي ن" },
  { "question": "زورو", "answer": "ز و ر و" },
  { "question": "ميرو", "answer": "م ي ر و" },
  { "question": "ريكي", "answer": "ر ي ك ي" },
  { "question": "نيشيميا", "answer": "ن ي ش ي م ي ا" },
  { "question": "سيرينا", "answer": "س ي ر ي ن ا" },
  { "question": "كانيكي", "answer": "ك ا ن ي ك ي" },
  { "question": "زينيتسو", "answer": "ز ي ن ي ت س و" },
  { "question": "نيزوكو", "answer": "ن ي ز و ك و" },
  { "question": "تانجيرو", "answer": "ت ا ن ج ي ر و" },
  { "question": "روبي", "answer": "ر و ب ي" },
  { "question": "آي", "answer": "آ ي" },
  { "question": "ال", "answer": "ا ل" },
  { "question": "لايت", "answer": "ل ا ي ت" },
  { "question": "لوفي", "answer": "ل و ف ي" },
  { "question": "روبين", "answer": "ر و ب ي ن" },
  { "question": "نامي", "answer": "ن ا م ي" },
  { "question": "مادارا", "answer": "م ا د ا ر ا" },
  { "question": "ميكو", "answer": "م ي ك و" },
  { "question": "انجيلو", "answer": "ا ن ج ي ل و" },
  { "question": "اكاي", "answer": "ا ك ا ي" },
  { "question": "كونان", "answer": "ك و ن ا ن" }
]
